photographypla.net 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - PhotographyPla.net

This privacy policy sets out how PhotographyPla.net uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from October 1, 2015.

## What We Collect

We may collect the following information:

  * your name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

Why do we need this information?

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

We may use cookies to participate in remarketing, which means visitors may see PhotographyPla.net advertisements (including ads by Google and other third parties) on other websites that participate in the display of advertisements. If you prefer, you can opt out of Google’s use of cookies from the [Google Ad Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

## Links to Other Websites

PhotographyPla.net may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
